{
    "id": "ae807d03724f46cbba057f186f582ad4",
    "title": "Can and Could Special Uses",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ....................... Mary coming.",
            "description": "When the verb see refers to perception, we do not normally use continuous forms.",
            "answers": [
                "can see",
                "am seeing",
                "see"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9ecf948f066b4c1fb668ea04685f3cda"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. somebody coming up the stairs?",
            "description": "When the verb hear refers to perception, we do not normally use progressive forms.",
            "answers": [
                "Are you hearing",
                "Can you hear"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5bba1416f76c4a91926fba4fb1921aa3"
        },
        {
            "question": "What did you put in the soup? I ………………… something funny.",
            "description": "When the verb taste refers to perception, we do not normally use progressive forms.",
            "answers": [
                "taste",
                "am tasting",
                "can taste"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "624f072ea5894de4a04d05c3c974ac6f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Suddenly I realized I ……………….. something burning.",
            "description": "When the verb smell refers to perception, we do not normally use progressive forms.",
            "answers": [
                "was smelling",
                "could smell"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4ca8d85a0e014db1a37be0a63b9ad776"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… what she wanted.",
            "description": "Know is not normally used with can/could.",
            "answers": [
                "knew",
                "could knew",
                "had known"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "322b004b97cf43f8b553a282a42c2ba1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… what she wanted.",
            "description": "Can and could are often used with the verb guess. ",
            "answers": [
                "guessed",
                "could guess",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b0058c3604c64e559b3571be47f8cce4"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………… she is British from her accent.",
            "description": "The expression ‘can tell’ means 'know'.",
            "answers": [
                "tell",
                "told",
                "can tell"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5775e38f83c64055b2f58f8698983e6e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ..................... what you are talking about.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can't understand",
                "don't understand",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6242979a3854478ba03832a822cc175f"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is an arrogant woman, but somehow you can’t ………………… her.",
            "description": "After can’t help, we use an -ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "help to like",
                "help like",
                "help liking"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "130fe1280af74927b901a14b534d4325"
        },
        {
            "question": "I couldn’t ………………. what they said.",
            "description": "After can’t / couldn't help, we use an ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "help to overhear",
                "help overhearing",
                "help overhear"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "afc14a49d0114fc08a642faef34c4f9a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t help ...................... what she wants.",
            "description": "After can’t help, we can use ‘but + infinitive without to’. This expression has the same meaning as ‘can’t help + ing form’.",
            "answers": [
                "but to wonder",
                "but wonder",
                "but wondering"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "df41a76b3510424aa95b99ceb60c1df2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can't help .......................... what I should do next.",
            "description": "The expression 'can't help + ing' has the same meaning as the expression 'can't help but + infinitive without to'.",
            "answers": [
                "but wonder",
                "wondering",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b9b22344716549289db13b79265d7c5c"
        }
    ]
}